Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/minh-tuyet-nguyen-b49b25150 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Regression Testing MongoDB Teamwork

Minh Tuyet Nguyen

Tester

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Quality Assurance Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Tortoise SVN, Critical Thinking, Linux, Postman API, and Microsoft Office. Strong engineering professional graduated from Can Tho University.

Experience

FPT Software
Software Tester
August 2021 - Present (3 years 8 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

TMA Solutions QA Engineer January 2018 - August 2021 (3 years 8 months) Hồ Chí Minh City

IVS Company QA Engineer October 2017 - November 2017 (2 months) Cần Thơ

Education

CAN THO UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's degree · (2016 - 2018)

APTECH Computer Education

Engineer's degree · (2011 - 2014)

CAN THO UNIVERSITY

The degree of Associate, Computer Software Engineering (2011 - 2014)